Guide to the Inge Morath Photographs and Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 1896-2001; Series I; 136.99; (550 boxes)
  - Contact Sheets
    - Personal Set
      - 1962-16. One Stop Banking (Roll 1) (Box 54)
      - 1962-17. Desmond Bernal, physicist; Isador Pfannkuchen; and Arthur Miller (Roll 1) (Box 54)
      - 1962-18. Lincoln Center (Roll 1) (Box 54)
      - 1962-19. Easter, advertising (Rolls 1-2) (Box 54)
      - 1962-20. New York Botanical Garden, Bronx, New York City, advertising (Roll 1) (Box 54)
      - 1962-21. Joan Maxine Miller Copeland, actress and the younger sister of Arthur Miller (Rolls 1-4) (Box 54)
      - 1962-22. Yankee Stadium, Bronx, New York City, advertising (Rolls 1-2) (Box 54)
      - 1962-23. Van Cortlandt House in the Bronx, New York City, advertising (Roll 1) (Box 54)
      - 1962-24. Salem, Massachusetts; Arthur Miller; and Joseph L. Rauh, Jr., lawyer in Westhampton, New York (Roll 1) (Box 54)
      - 1962-25. Alice in Wonderland (Roll 1) (Box 54)
      - 1962-26. Flower cart, advertising (Roll 1) (Box 54)
      - 1962-27. Doris Caesar, sculptor, in Litchfield, Connecticut (Roll 1) (Box 54)
      - 1962-28. Maternity hospital, advertising (Roll 1) (Box 54)
      - 1962-28. Storm, Long Island, New York (No rolls recorded, color photographs) (Box 60)
      - 1962-29. Shopping Fifth Avenue, New York City, advertising (Roll 1) (Box 54)
      - 1962-30. City College of New York, advertising (Rolls 1-2) (Box 54)
      - 1962-31. Brooklyn Bridge (Rolls 1-5) (Box 50)
      - 1962-31. Brooklyn Bridge (Rolls 1-5) (Box 54)
      - 1962-32. Masks made by Saul Steinberg, cartoonist and illustrator, Sigrid "Gigi" Spaeth, Arthur Miller, and Roxbury, Connecticut (Rolls 1-10) (Box 50)
      - 1962-32. Masks made by Saul Steinberg, cartoonist and illustrator, Sigrid "Gigi" Spaeth, Arthur Miller, and Roxbury, Connecticut (Rolls 1-10) (Box 54)
      - 1962-33. Story destroyed by Inge Morath (No rolls recorded) (Box 54)
      - 1962-34. Suburban woman (Rolls 1-8) (Box 54)
      - 1962-35. Personal photographs (No rolls recorded, color photographs) (Box 54)
      - 1962-36. Arthur Miller; Elia Kazan, director, producer, writer and actor; and Boris Aronson, scenic designer (Rolls 1-4) (Box 50)
      - 1962-37. Bankers Trust cover, advertising (Rolls 1-2) (Box 54)
      - 1962-38. Bowling Green concert, advertising (Roll 1) (Box 54)
      - 1962-39. City Island, Bronx, New York City, advertising (Rolls 1-2) (Box 55)
      - 1962-40. Corn field, Staten Island, advertising (Rolls 1-2) (Box 55)
      - 1962-41. Automobile, advertising (Roll 1) (Box 55)
      - 1962-42. Lincoln Center, advertising (Roll 1) (Box 55)
      - 1962-43. Rebecca Miller (Rolls 1-11) (Box 50)
      - 1962-43. Rebecca Miller (Rolls 1-11) (Box 55)
      - 1962-44. El Cid, advertising (Roll 1) (Box 55)
      - 1962-45. Fire boat, advertising (Rolls 1-2) (Box 55)
      - 1962-46. Battery Park, New York City, advertising (Rolls 1-2) (Box 55)
      - 1962-47. Ice skating, Prospect Park, Brooklyn, New York City, advertising (Rolls 1-2) (Box 55)
      - 1962-48. Sheepshead Bay, Brooklyn, New York City, advertising (Rolls 1-3) (Box 55)
      - 1962-49. General store in Roxbury, Connecticut (Rolls 1-3) (Box 55)
      - 1962-50. Washington Bridge, New York City (Rolls 1-3) (Box 55)
      - 1962-51. Woman fashion editor and man buyer, advertising (Rolls 1-2) (Box 55)
      - 1962-52. New York views, advertising (Rolls 1-2) (Box 55)
      - 1962-53. Bankers Trust annual report, advertising (Rolls 1-4) (Box 55)
      - 1962-54. Christmas tree buying, advertising (Roll 1) (Box 55)
      - 1962-55. Christmas in Brooklyn Heights, New York City, advertising (Roll 1) (Box 55)
      - 1963-01. Bankers Trust building and escalator, advertising (Roll 1) (Box 55)
      - 1963-02. Overseas personnel, advertising for the Donahue & Coe advertising agency (Rolls 1-4) (Box 55)
      - 1963-03. Preparation in Roxbury, Connecticut for After the Fall, by Arthur Miller, directed by Elia Kazan, and produced by Robert Whitehead, at the Repertory Theatre of Lincoln Center, New York City (Rolls 1-5) (Box 55)
      - 1963-03. Preparation in Roxbury, Connecticut for After the Fall, by Arthur Miller, directed by Elia Kazan, and produced by Robert Whitehead, at the Repertory Theatre of Lincoln Center, New York City (Rolls 1-5) (Box 56)
      - 1963-04. Arthur Miller and Rebecca Miller (Rolls 1-30) (Box 50)
      - 1963-04. Arthur Miller and Rebecca Miller (Rolls 1-30) (Box 55)
      - 1963-04. Arthur Miller and Rebecca Miller (Rolls 1-30) (Box 56)
      - 1963-04. Grand Army Plaza in Prospect Park, Brooklyn, New York City, advertising (Roll 1), 1962 (Box 53)
      - 1963-05. Rowe of Bond Street, London, England (Rolls 1-5) (Box 57)
      - 1963-06. Painter and child model portraits, advertising (Rolls 1-2) (Box 57)
      - 1963-07. Lawyer's office, advertising (Roll 1) (Box 57)
      - 1963-08. Construction, advertising (Roll 1) (Box 57)
      - 1963-09. Roxbury, Connecticut (Roll 1) (Box 57)
      - 1963-10. New York International Airport, Anderson Field, also known as Idlewild Airport, New York City, advertising (Roll 1) (Box 57)
      - 1963-11. Photographer shooting models, advertising (Rolls 1-2) (Box 57)
      - 1963-12. Polo, advertising (Rolls 1-2) (Box 57)
      - 1963-13. Young New York model, Jane Ellen Miller, daughter of Arthur Miller and Mary Grace Slattery (Rolls 1-2) (Box 57)
      - 1963-14. Cutter, dress manufacturer (Rolls 1-2) (Box 57)
      - 1963-15. Hospital, advertising (Rolls 1-2) (Box 57)
      - 1963-16. Director and actors, advertising (Rolls 1-2) (Box 57)
      - 1963-17. Gun cleaning, advertising (Rolls 1-2) (Box 57)
      - 1963-18. Bank safe, advertising (Roll 1) (Box 57)
      - 1963-19. Mother and child riding, advertising (Rolls 1-2) (Box 57)
      - 1963-20. Alexander Calder, sculptor, including his wife, Louisa James Calder, Arthur Miller, and photographers Gjon Mili and Henri Cartier-Bresson (Rolls 1-6) (Box 57)
      - 1963-21. Mr. Roberts, advertising (Rolls 1-2) (Box 57)
      - 1963-22. Kennel, advertising (Rolls 1-4) (Box 57)
      - 1963-23. Brooklyn Bridge (Rolls 1-8) (Box 57)
      - 1963-24. Tennis, advertising (Rolls 1-3) (Box 57)
      - 1963-25. Sailing, advertising (Rolls 1-6) (Box 57)
      - 1963-26. After the Fall, by Arthur Miller, directed by Elia Kazan, and produced by Robert Whitehead, at the Repertory Theatre of Lincoln Center, New York City (Rolls 1-110) (Box 56)
        Includes Joseph "Jo" Mielziner, scenic and lighting designer; S. N. Behrman playwright and author; David Amram, composer and musician; José Quintero, director; and Carlotta Monterey O'Neill, widow of Eugene O'Neill, as well as actresses Faye Dunaway, Salome Jens, Zohra Lampert, and Barbara Loden; and actors Jason Robards and Hal Holbrook.
      - 1963-26. After the Fall, by Arthur Miller, directed by Elia Kazan, and produced by Robert Whitehead, at the Repertory Theatre of Lincoln Center, New York City (Rolls 1-110) (Box 58)
      - 1963-26. After the Fall, by Arthur Miller, directed by Elia Kazan, and produced by Robert Whitehead, at the Repertory Theatre of Lincoln Center, New York City (Rolls 1-110) (Box 59)
      - 1963-27. Connecticut nursery (Rolls 1-6) (Box 60)
      - 1963-29. Sculling regatta, advertising (Rolls 1-2) (Box 60)
      - 1963-30. Jane Ellen Miller, daughter of Arthur Miller and Mary Grace Slattery, in New York City (Rolls 1-2) (Box 60)
      - 1963-31. Boris Aronson, scenic designer for theatre (Rolls 1-4) (Box 60)
      - 1963-32. Football, advertising (Rolls 1-4) (Box 60)
      - 1963-44. Wagner College, New York City, advertising (Rolls 1-4) (Box 51)
      - 1964-01. Greece and Rue de la Chaise in Paris, France (Rolls 1-16) (Box 60)
        Includes Arthur Miller
      - 1964-01. Greece and Rue de la Chaise in Paris, France (Rolls 1-16) (Box 61)
      - 1964-02. Alexander Calder, sculptor (Roll 1) (Box 60)
        Includes David Amram, composer and musician, as well as views of the Chelsea Hotel in New York City, and Saché, France
      - 1964-02. Alexander Calder, sculptor (Roll 1) (Box 61)
      - 1964-03. Honfleur and Tôtes, France (Rolls 1-3) (Box 60)
        Includes David Amram, composer, conductor, multi-instrumentalist, and author
      - 1964-03. Honfleur and Tôtes, France (Rolls 1-3) (Box 61)
      - 1964-04. Frankfurt Auschwitz trials in Frankfurt, Germany (Rolls 1-2) (Box 60)
        Includes Hessian Generalstaatsanwalt (State Attorney General) Fritz Bauer and sociologist Theodor W. Adorno
      - 1964-04. Frankfurt Auschwitz trials in Frankfurt, Germany (Rolls 1-2) (Box 61)
      - 1964-05. Rebecca Miller and Arthur Miller (Rolls 1-8) (Box 60)
      - 1964-05. Rebecca Miller and Arthur Miller (Rolls 1-8) (Box 61)
      - 1964-06. Woodbury, Connecticut (Rolls 1-26) (Box 60)
        Includes theater director and critic Harold Clurman and Arthur Miller
        Many images appear in Inge Morath and Arthur Miller, In the Country (New York: Viking Press, 1977)
      - 1964-06. Woodbury, Connecticut (Rolls 1-26) (Box 61)
      - 1964-06. Woodbury, Connecticut (Rolls 1-26) (Box 63)
      - 1964-07. Arthur Miller; William Styron, novelist and essayist; and Ralph Ellison, novelist, literary critic, and writer (Roll 1) (Box 60)
      - 1964-07. Arthur Miller; William Styron, novelist and essayist; and Ralph Ellison, novelist, literary critic, and writer (Roll 1) (Box 61)
      - 1964-08. Model for New Fountain, by Alexander Calder (Rolls 1-12, lacking Rolls 6-7) (Box 60)
        Includes Calder putting out the model
      - 1964-08. Model for New Fountain, by Alexander Calder (Rolls 1-12, lacking Rolls 6-7) (Box 61)
      - 1964-10. George Segal, actor (Rolls 1-4) (Box 62)
      - 1964-11. Arthur Miller (Roll 1) (Box 62)
      - 1964-12. John F. Wharton, lawyer in entertainment law (Rolls 1-3) (Box 62)
      - 1964-12. John F. Wharton, lawyer in entertainment law (Rolls 1-3) (Box 63)
      - 1964-13. Claudia Alta Taylor "Lady Bird" Johnson, First Lady of the United States (Rolls 1-2) (Box 62)
      - 1964-14. Loan advertisement (Rolls 1-2) (Box 62)
        Includes a flute player
      - 1964-15. International Rescue Committee, society ball (Rolls 1-4) (Box 62)
        Includes director Mike Nichols, journalist and activist Gloria Steinem, and pianist Peter Duchin
      - 1964-16. Gala Pension Fund Benefit Concert, New York Philharmonic (Rolls 1-4) (Box 62)
        Includes Jean Peters, actress, and Frederick Heyworth Cripps, 3rd Baron Parmoor
      - 1964-17. Incident at Vichy, by Arthur Miller, at the ANTA Washington Square Theatre in New York City (Rolls 1-24) (Box 62)
        Includes scene designer Boris Arenson, and actors David Wayne, Joseph Wiseman, and Hal Holbrook
      - 1964-17. Incident at Vichy, by Arthur Miller, at the ANTA Washington Square Theatre in New York City (Rolls 1-24) (Box 63)
      - 1964-18. Blair House, Washington, D.C. (Rolls 1-5) (Box 62)
        Includes diplomat Angier Biddle Duke and Mrs. Bliss
      - 1964-18. Blair House, Washington, D.C. (Rolls 1-5) (Box 63)
      - 1964-19. April in Paris Ball (Rolls 1-7) (Box 62)
        Includes Mary Woodard Lasker, health activist and philanthropist; and Sammy Davis, Jr., entertainer; as well as actresses Paulette Goddard and Beatrice Lillie
      - 1964-20. Alexander Calder: A Retrospective Exhibition at the Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum in New York City (Roll 1) (Box 62)
      - 1964-21. Jessica Walter, actress (Rolls 1-3) (Box 62)
      - 1964-22. Sheridan Hamilton-Temple-Blackwood, 5th Marquess of Dufferin and his wife, Serena Belinda Rosemary Guinness (Rolls 1-4) (Box 62)
        Includes painters Patricia Coffin, Helen Frankenthaler, and Frank Strella
      - 1964-23. Adriana Maliponte, soprano (Rolls 1-4) (Box 62)
      - 1964-24. C. D. B. Bryan, author and journalist (Rolls 1-4) (Box 62)
      - 1964-25. Young farmer in Oneida County, New York? (No rolls recorded, color photographs) (Box 62)
      - 1964-26. Marni Nixon, soprano (Rolls 1-5) (Box 62)
      - 1965-01. Alice Roosevelt Longworth, writer and socialite (Rolls 1-4) (Box 64)
        Includes Washington, D.C.
      - 1965-01A. Snow in Paris, France (Rolls 1-2) (Box 64)
      - 1965-02. René Shapshak, sculptor (Roll 1) (Box 64)
      - 1965-03. Arthur Miller and Laurence Olivier, actor, director, and producer (Rolls 1-2) (Box 64)
      - 1965-04. After the Fall, by Arthur Miller, directed by Elia Kazan, at Repertory Theatre of Lincoln Center, New York City (Rolls 1-4) (Box 64)
        Includes actress and director Marie Bell, and Luchino Visconti, director and screenwriter
      - 1965-05. Soviet Union (Rolls 1-28) (Box 64)
        Includes Andrei Voznesensky, poet and author, and his wife, Zoya Boguslavskaya, probably at a performance based on his collection of poetry, Antimiry ( Anti-worlds ) at the Taganka Theater, Moscow, on May 5, 1965.
        Others include Nikolay Akimov, theater director and scenic designer; Ilya Ehrenburg, author; Yekaterina Furtseva, Minister of Culture; Daniil Granin, author; Lev Kassil, author; Aram Khachaturian, composer and conductor; Pavel Korin, painter; Mikhail Mikhaylovich Gerasimov; archaeologist and anthropologist; Sergo Mikoyan, historian; Konstantin Simonov, author and poet; Oleg Yefremov, actor and producer; and Yevgeny Yevtushenko, poet and author
      - 1965-05. Soviet Union (Rolls 1-28) (Box 65)
      - 1965-06. Arthur Miller in Paris, France (Roll 1) (Box 64)
      - 1965-06. Arthur Miller in Paris, France (Roll 1) (Box 65)
      - 1965-07. Alexander Calder, sculptor, in France (Rolls 1-2) (Box 64)
        Includes a market in Warsaw, Poland, and Liège, France
      - 1965-07. Alexander Calder, sculptor, in France (Rolls 1-2) (Box 65)
      - 1965-08. Kentucky (Rolls 1-28) (Box 64)
        Includes frontier nurses
      - 1965-08. Kentucky (Rolls 1-28) (Box 65)
      - 1965-09. Connecticut (Rolls 1-31) (Box 64)
        Includes images for Inge Morath and Arthur Miller, In the Country (New York: Viking Press, 1977)
        Also includes Clare Leighton, artist and author; and Olga Andreyev Carlisle, author; as well as critic John Gruen and his wife, painter Jane Wilson
      - 1965-09. Connecticut (Rolls 1-31) (Box 65)
      - 1965-10. American Jewish writers (Rolls 1-15) (Box 65)
        Includes Bruce Jay Friedman, Joseph Heller, Alfred Kazin, Norman Mailer, Bernard Malamud, Norman Podhoretz, and Philip Roth
      - 1965-10. American Jewish writers (Rolls 1-15) (Box 66)
      - 1965-11. New York (Rolls 1-3) (Box 65)
      - 1965-11. New York (Rolls 1-3) (Box 66)
      - 1965-12. Saul Steinberg, cartoonist and illustrator (Rolls 1-2) (Box 66)
      - 1965-13. Soviet Union (Rolls 1-6, lacking Roll 5) (Box 66)
      - 1965-14. Arthur Miller (No rolls recorded, color photographs) (Box 66)
      - 1965-15. Corby Pleasant from JAX fashions (Roll 1) (Box 66)
      - 1965-16. Café La Mama in the Lower East Side, New York City (Rolls 1-5) (Box 66)
        Includes Jane Wilson, as well as sons of Luis Buñuel, Juan-Luis Buñuel and Rafael Buñuel
      - 1965-17. Croton Distributing Reservoir (also known as the Murray Hill Reservoir) in New York City related to a story about drought (Rolls 1-2) (Box 66)
      - 1965-18. "Ten Best Dressed Rooms" created by members of the American Institute of Interior Designers at the National Design Center in New York City (Rolls 1-2, and 10) (Box 66)
        Includes Sybil Burton Christopher, actress and theater director
      - 1965-19. Pope Paul IV in New York (Rolls 1-3) (Box 66)
        Includes people on streets
      - 1965-20. New Haven, Connecticut, development (Rolls 1-11) (Box 66)
        Includes Vice President Hubert Humphrey
      - 1965-21. Picasso Painting for Britannica (No rolls recorded, color photographs) (Box 66)
      - 1965-22. Karen Sustak (No rolls recorded, color photographs) (Box 66)
      - 1965-23. Arthur Miller (Rolls 1-2) (Box 66)
      - 1965-24. Recording Death of a Salesman (Rolls 1-15) (Box 66)
        Includes actress Mildred Dunnock, as well as actors Lee Cobb and Dustin Hoffman
      - 1965-25. Xerox Corporation stockholder meeting, called "65X" (No rolls recorded) (Box 66)
      - 1966-01. Incident at Vichy, by Arthur Miller, at the Phoenix Theatre, London, England (Rolls 1-11) (Box 67)
        Includes Alec Guinness, actor; and Anthony Quayle, actor and director
      - 1966-01A. Rebecca Miller in Paris, France; Roxbury, Connecticut; and Vienna, Austria (No rolls recorded) (Box 67)
      - 1966-02. Christmas market in Piazza Navona, Rome, Italy (Roll 1) (Box 67)
        Includes Rebecca Miller
      - 1966-03. Baroque Eisenstadt, Austria (Rolls 1-1A) (Box 67)
        Includes Arthur Miller and Rebecca Miller; Eisenstadt and Maria Enzersdorf Austria; and Prince Josef Schwarzenberg III
      - 1966-04. Robert Josephi (Rolls 1-4) (Box 67)
        Includes Rebecca Miller in Paris, France
      - 1966-05. Andrei Voznesensky, poet and writer (Rolls 1-5) (Box 67)
        Includes Patricia Blake, actress; Max Hayward, translator; and William Styron, author; as well as Henry Carlisle, translator and novelist, and his wife, author Olga Andreyev Carlisle
      - 1966-06. Alexander Calder, sculptor (No rolls recorded, color photographs) (Box 67)
      - 1966-07. Connecticut (Roll 1) (Box 67)
        Includes Alexander Calder, sculptor; Olga Andreyev Carlisle, author; Philip Evergood, artist; Stephen Minot, author; and William vanden Heuvel, attorney, author, and diplomat
      - 1966-08. PEN International Meeting (Rolls 1-21) (Box 67)
        Includes members of PEN International: Edward Albee, Saul Bellow, Malcolm Cowley, Hilde Domin, Ralph Ellison, Carlos Fuentes, Rosamond Lehmann, Arthur Miller, Marco Antonio Montes d'Oca, Pablo Neruda, Ignazio Silone, Hilde Spiel, and John Steinbeck
      - 1966-09. Montessori School (Rolls 1-5, lacking Roll 1) (Box 67)
      - 1966-10. Fourth of July (No rolls recorded, color photographs) (Box 67)
      - 1966-11. Arthur Miller in Connecticut (Roll 1) (Box 67)
      - 1966-12. Camera, advertising, and Connecticut (Rolls 1-4) (Box 67)
      - 1966-13. Opening of the Metropolitan Opera House at Lincoln Center, New York City (Rolls 1-6) (Box 67)
      - 1966-14. Saul Steinberg, cartoonist and illustrator, and a nose mask (Roll 1) (Box 67)
      - 1966-15. Philip Evergood, artist and author (Rolls 1-2) (Box 67)
      - 1966-16. Ira Levin, author, dramatist, and songwriter (Rolls 1-2) (Box 67)
      - 1966-17. Yevgeny Yevtushenko, poet and author (Rolls 1-4) (Box 67)
        Includes Arthur Miller; Saul Steinberg, cartoonist and illustrator; and William Styron, author; as well as John Updike, author, and his wife, Mary E. Pennington Updike
      - 1966-18. Brighton, England (Roll 1)
      - 1967-01. Connecticut (Rolls 1-37) (Box 68)
        Includes Ulu Grosbard, director and producer; Olga Andreyev Carlisle, author; Elia Kazan, director, producer, writer and actor; Barbara Loden, actress and director; Arthur Miller; Louis Untermeyer, poet; and Saul Steinberg, cartoonist and illustrator
      - 1967-02. William Styron, novelist and essayist (Rolls 1-4) (Box 68)
      - 1967-03. Louis Untermeyer, poet, anthologist, critic, and editor (Rolls 1-2) (Box 68)
      - 1967-04. Haile Selassie, Emperor of Ethiopia (Rolls 1-6) (Box 68)
      - 1967-05. Barbara Loden, actress, model, and director (Rolls 1-4) (Box 68)
      - 1967-06. Andrei Voznesensky, poet and writer (Roll 1) (Box 68)
      - 1967-07. Alexei Kosygin, Soviet statesman, at the headquarters of the United Nations in New York City (Rolls 1-5) (Box 68)
      - 1967-08. Wedding of Thomas Guinzburg, editor and publisher, and Rusty Unger, author (Rolls 1-3) (Box 68)
        Includes Leonard Lyons, newspaper columnist; and Lauren Bacall, actress; Arthur Miller, and Ulu Grossbard, director
      - 1967-09. Stratford Shakespeare Festival in Stratford, Ontario, Canada (Rolls 1-15) (Box 68)
        Includes Zoe Caldwell, actress, and Christopher Plummer, actor
      - 1967-10. Classical antiquities collection of Barbara Fleischman and Lawrence Fleischman (Rolls 1-3) (Box 69)
      - 1967-11. Soviet Union (Rolls 1-57) (Box 69)
        Includes Vasily Aksyonov, novelist; Joseph Brodsky, poet and essayist; David Kakabadze, artist; Valentin Kataev, novelist and dramatist; Yuri Lyubimov, actor and director associated with the Taganka Theatre; Nadezhda Mandelstam, author; Maya Plisetskaya, ballet dancer, choreographer, ballet director, and actress; Ernst Neizvestny, artist; Andrei Voznesensky, poet, and his wife, Zoya Boguslavskaya; and Yevgeny Yevtushenko, poet, and his wife, Galina Sokol-Lukonina.
        Also includes performance of "Ten Days That Shook the World" at the Taganka Theatre played by Nikolay Gubenko on November 3, 1967
      - 1967-12. The Price, by Arthur Miller at the Morosco Theatre, New York City (Rolls 1-44, lacking Roll 20) (Box 69)
        Includes actors David Burns, Pat Hingle, Arthur Kennedy, Kate Reid, and Jack Warden
      - 1967-13. Lower Austria (Rolls 1-2) (Box 69)
        Includes Rebecca Miller and Inge Morath's parents, Mathilde Wiesler Morath and Edgar Morath
      - 1968-01. Connecticut (Rolls 1-24) (Box 70)
        Includes Ingrid Bergman, actress; Peter Blume, painter and sculptor; Alexander Calder, sculptor, and his wife Louisa James Calder; Henry Carlisle, translator and novelist, and his wife, author Olga Andreyev Carlisle; John Cheever, novelist; William Sloane Coffin, clergyman and activist; Malcolm Cowley, novelist; Francine du Plessix Gray, author and critic; Allen Ginsberg, poet; Thomas Guinzburg, editor and publisher; Matthew Josephson, journalist and historian; Arthur Miller; Alex North, composer; Paul O'Dwyer, politician and lawyer; Robert C. Osborn, artist and author, and his wife, museum director Elodie Courter Osborn; Hans Richter, painter; David Schoenbrun, journalist; Harrison E. Salisbury, author and journalist, and his wife, author Charlotte Young Salisbury; Saul Steinberg, cartoonist and illustrator; William Styron, novelist and essayist, and his wife, poet Rose Burgunder Styron; Louis Untermeyer, poet; Yevgeny Yevtushenko, poet; and E. B. White, author
      - 1968-02. Anti-Vietnam War rally and march in New Haven, Connecticut (Rolls 1-2) (Box 70)
        Includes William Sloane Coffin, clergyman and activist; Arthur Miller; and Stephen Minot, author
      - 1968-03. Robert Anderson (Rolls 1-3) (Box 70)
        Includes William Sloane Coffin, clergyman and activist; and Arthur Miller
      - 1968-04. Mexico (Rolls 1-9) (Box 70)
        Includes Marco Antonio Montes de Oca, poet and painter; Salvador Novo, author and poet; José Revueltas, author; David Alfaro Siqueiros, painter; and Yevgeny Yevtushenko, poet and author
      - 1968-05. Eugene McCarthy presidential campaign (Rolls 1-23) (Box 70)
        Includes Alan Arkin, actor, director, and musician; John Bayley, author and critic; John N. Dempsey, governor of Connecticut; Joseph Duffey, educator; Jules Feiffer, cartoonist; Allen Ginsberg, poet; Richard N. Goodwin, author and speechwriter; Ella T. Grasso, Secretary of the State of Connecticut; Lillian Hellman, dramatist and screenwriter; Dustin Hoffman, actor; Paul O'Dwyer, politician and lawyer; Paula Prentiss, actress; Elizabeth Hardwick, author and critic; Abraham A. Ribicoff, United States Senator from Connecticut; William Styron, author; and Richard Wilbur, poet
      - 1968-06. Whale at the New York Aquarium in Coney Island, and Alex Lieberman, magazine editor, publisher, painter, photographer, and sculptor (Rolls 1-3) (Box 70)
      - 1968-07. Funeral of Robert F. Kennedy (Rolls 1-11) (Box 70)
      - 1968-08. Henry Carlisle, translator, novelist, and activist (Rolls 1-2) (Box 70)
      - 1969-01. Connecticut (Rolls 1-44) (Box 71)